Extremely efficient programmer with over 4 years of experience working in the computer science industry. Lead programmer of Schüco's virtual reality project and of +5 other diverse projects. Using critical thinking, proficient programming, and knowledge of the industry to benefit the company's sales, appearance, and teamwork in a fairly major way.

# **Experience**

# 2017-09 - present

# **VR Programmer / Programmer**

Schuco USA LLP

### Responsibilities:

- Lead Programmer on Schüco's Virtual World, that increased the companies interaction rate at trade fairs by 30%.
  - Using the HTC Vive, Unreal Engine, and C++ to develop a virtual reality experience of the Schüco products.
- Developed a Launcher in C# which incorporates a database manager created MySQL.
- Developed and managed a database of over +50 customers, and partners.
- Programmed an IFC to Virtual Reality application for architect models.

### 2017-03 -2017-06

# **Graphics Programmer / Engine Programmer**

Code Bros Studios

Helped develop Act of Arms, a real-time strategy game based in medieval times, developed in our house-made Hush Puppy Engine.

### Responsibilities:

- Lead Graphics Programmer on Act of Arms.
- Developed a component based engine utilizing DirectX and C++.
- Coded graphic shaders in HLSL.
- Programmed an FBX Importer and Exporter.
- Coded the logic for the camera movement.

# 2016-06 -2016-08

# **Gameplay Programmer**

Spotlight Studio

Helped develop Light in the Dark, a top-down, light-based dungeon crawler where you have dropped into the monster-filled nightmare of Lux. Armed with only a flashlight and your wits, you must sneak your way out of the nightmare alive.

### Responsibilities:

- Lead Gameplay Programmer on Light in the Dark, developed using Unity 3D and C#.
- Level Designed the vast majority of the levels all through the game.

# **Education**

# 2015-09 -2017-06

# Full Sail University, Game Development - Bachelor of Science

### **Related Coursework:**

- Learned various languages, for example, C#, C++, Java.
- Learned graphics languages DirectX and OpenGL.
- Learned engine development from scratch, which I took that knowledge to help build the Hush Puppy Engine for the game Act of Arms.
- Learned different AI techniques, including pathfinding and search algorithms.
- Studied basic computer networking for games.
- Studied database structures and algorithms.

# Timothy Felice

Programmer

# **Personal Info**

#### Address:

20432 Hamlin st. Winnetka, CA 91306

**Phone** 

(908) 461-2670

### E-mail

TimothyMFelice@gmail.com

#### **Personal Website**

www.TFelice.info

### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/Timothy-Felice/

# **Computer Skills**

Virtual Reality Development

Advanced

C++ / C#

Advanced

Unreal Engine / Unity 3D

Advanced

DirectX / OpenGL

Intermediate

Java / MySQL

Intermediate

# **Skills**

Teamwork

Advanced

Critical Thinking

Advanced

Quick Learner

Advanced

Team Leadership

Intermediate